[
    {
        "problem_id": 0,
        "problem": "What color is the chair in the kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1,
        "problem": "What color is the wooden chair in the kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 2,
        "problem": "Where is the brown wooden chair placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at head of long rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 3,
        "problem": "What color is the armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 4,
        "problem": "What color are the lower kitchen cabinets? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 5,
        "problem": "What is under the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> kitchen cabinets </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 6,
        "problem": "What is on the wall of the kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 7,
        "problem": "On what part of the kitchen is the black square tv located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 8,
        "problem": "What is on the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 9,
        "problem": "What is the top of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> under black rectangular tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 10,
        "problem": "Where is the tv on the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above thin brown wooden table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 11,
        "problem": "What color is the tv above a thin table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 12,
        "problem": "What is below the big black tv? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> thin brown wooden table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 13,
        "problem": "What is under the long kitchen counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown rectangular kitchen cabinets </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 14,
        "problem": "What is at the end of the table close to the tv? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> thin brown wooden table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 15,
        "problem": "What color is the chair by tv? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 16,
        "problem": "What type of counter is below two windows? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> kitchen </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 17,
        "problem": "What color is the trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> grey </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 18,
        "problem": "Where does the trash can sit in the kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right of table under tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 19,
        "problem": "What material is the refrigerator made of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stainless steel </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 20,
        "problem": "Where does the trash can sit? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> between jotted out wall on right and narrow table on left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 21,
        "problem": "How many chairs face the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 10 brown chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 22,
        "problem": "Which chair is closest to the tv? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 23,
        "problem": "Which chairs are on the same side of the room as the trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 brown chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 24,
        "problem": "How many chairs are at the end of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 25,
        "problem": "What color is the refrigerator? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stainless steel </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 26,
        "problem": "What type of kitchen cabinets are in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wood </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 27,
        "problem": "What appliance is built into the top of the lower kitchen cabinets? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stainless steel sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 28,
        "problem": "Where is the tall chair on the right of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of narrow table tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 29,
        "problem": "Where are the two chairs in front of one another? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> end table closest to door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 30,
        "problem": "What is in the middle of the kitchen cabinets? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 31,
        "problem": "What is in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> cabinet refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 32,
        "problem": "What color table is to the left of a trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 33,
        "problem": "What type of table does the tv sit above? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> thin brown wooden table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 34,
        "problem": "Where does the console table sit in the kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> underneath black rectangular tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 35,
        "problem": "Where does the console table sit? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> up against wall underneath black rectangular tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 36,
        "problem": "What color is the counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 37,
        "problem": "What is on the same side of the kitchen as the counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 38,
        "problem": "What type of freezer does the refrigerator have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bottom freezer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 39,
        "problem": "What shape is the refrigerator on the left of a kitchen counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> rectangular </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 40,
        "problem": "Where is one of the refrigerators located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left of window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 41,
        "problem": "What is above the brown cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> kitchen counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 42,
        "problem": "What type of refrigerator is on the right of a kitchen counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stainless steel refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 43,
        "problem": "To what side of a kitchen counter is the refrigerator located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner to right of windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 44,
        "problem": "What color does the refridgerator appear to be? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 45,
        "problem": "The refridgerator sits next to a pair of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 46,
        "problem": "Where is a tall trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left of double doors </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 47,
        "problem": "What is below the windows nearest the refrigerator? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 48,
        "problem": "What is at the end of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 49,
        "problem": "Where is the chair closest to the front? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> end of table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 50,
        "problem": "Where is the chair located on the side of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> between tv and table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 51,
        "problem": "The chair on the side of the table near the ovens will be what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> warmer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 52,
        "problem": "Where is the chair at the head of the table located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 53,
        "problem": "What is behind the brown chair at the head of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 54,
        "problem": "What shape is the tv above a small thin table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> square </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 55,
        "problem": "What is the tv above? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 56,
        "problem": "How many brown chairs are behind the long table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 57,
        "problem": "What type of refrigerator is it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stanless steel </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 58,
        "problem": "What is the black kitchen counter on top of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> cabinets </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 59,
        "problem": "Where is the brown cabinet located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on bottom of wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 60,
        "problem": "What is the long table surrounded by? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 10 brown wooden office chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 61,
        "problem": "Where is the brown chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> around long brown wooden table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 62,
        "problem": "What color is the chair that is placed next to a table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 63,
        "problem": "What is beneath the tv? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 64,
        "problem": "What is next to the table beneath the tv? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 65,
        "problem": "What color are the kitchen cabinets? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 66,
        "problem": "Where is the chair with no arms ? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at high table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 67,
        "problem": "What is above the small table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 68,
        "problem": "What is in the room that has ten chairs pulled up to it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wooden table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 69,
        "problem": "How many chairs does the large table in the room have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 10 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 70,
        "problem": "How many brown chairs are on the left of the brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 71,
        "problem": "What is on the front of the brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 72,
        "problem": "What is pulled up to the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 73,
        "problem": "What is the position of the chair from the right of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> away </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 74,
        "problem": "To what side of a table is the trash can located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind it </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 75,
        "problem": "What type of refrigerator is in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stanless steel </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 76,
        "problem": "What is to the left of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 77,
        "problem": "Where is the chair with no arms that is pushed furthest away from table located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of long narrow table against wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 78,
        "problem": "Where does the brown cabinet set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> beside refrigerator furthest on left sits to right ground </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 79,
        "problem": "What part of the room has a fridge to its right? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right corner wall adjacent to tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 80,
        "problem": "What is the brown table surrounded by? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown padded chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 81,
        "problem": "Where do the chairs set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> around long brown rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 82,
        "problem": "What kind of tv is affixed to the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black rectangular widescreen tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 83,
        "problem": "Where is the big screen tv affixed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 84,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the kitchen counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 85,
        "problem": "Where is the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> by wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 86,
        "problem": "Where is the chair pulled into? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> end of long brown rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 87,
        "problem": "How many chairs are to the left of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 brown office chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 88,
        "problem": "How many chairs are to the right of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 brown office chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 89,
        "problem": "What is the chair in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> thin brown wooden table and black rectangular tv </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 90,
        "problem": "Where is the brown chair located on the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at end of table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0011_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 91,
        "problem": "What color is the wooden desk on the first row of the classroom? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown wooden </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 92,
        "problem": "Where is the beige wooden desk placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> up against wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 93,
        "problem": "What is placed in front of a desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black office chair with no arms </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 94,
        "problem": "Where is an office chair placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to brown rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 95,
        "problem": "Where is the wooden steel desk located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back center of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 96,
        "problem": "What color is the office chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 97,
        "problem": "Where is the black office chair placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on side of wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 98,
        "problem": "What is next to the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armless checkerboard chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 99,
        "problem": "The office chair is placed next to what part of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on side of wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 100,
        "problem": "What is in front of the windows? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> windowsill </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 101,
        "problem": "What is the backpack on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 102,
        "problem": "What is the water bottle on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 103,
        "problem": "What color is the wooden steel desk in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 104,
        "problem": "On what part of the room is the beige wooden steel desk located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> under small whiteboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 105,
        "problem": "Where is the short table located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at front of room under large whiteboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 106,
        "problem": "Does the chair have arms? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> no </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 107,
        "problem": "Where is a wooden chair with no arms located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> no </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 108,
        "problem": "What type of table is located near a single chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> rectangle </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 109,
        "problem": "How close is the single chair to the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> up against wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 110,
        "problem": "Where is one end of the tan table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to black office chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 111,
        "problem": "What is the patterned chair facing? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown rectangular wooden table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 112,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the black chair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> around tables </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 113,
        "problem": "What is the table in front of two chairs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 114,
        "problem": "How many other chairs does the polka dotted chair set between? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> between 2 other chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 115,
        "problem": "What kind of chairs are set around the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair with no arms </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 116,
        "problem": "Where does the black chair set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on side of wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 117,
        "problem": "What color is the dotted chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black and white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 118,
        "problem": "Where does the polka dotted chair set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in middle of 2 right desks </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 119,
        "problem": "What type of table has a wood look? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wood table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 120,
        "problem": "The 3rd table is on the side close to what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> rectangular windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 121,
        "problem": "Where is the armless checkerboard blue padded chair in class? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of third rectangular brown table in room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 122,
        "problem": "Where is the long table on one end? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> up against wall near windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 123,
        "problem": "What is facing the chair with no arms? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 124,
        "problem": "How many chairs are behind the long table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 black office chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 125,
        "problem": "What type of table is next to a patterned chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black office chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 126,
        "problem": "What kind of chair is next to the wooden table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black office chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 127,
        "problem": "Where is the table in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> up against wall next to windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 128,
        "problem": "What is around the table in the back left of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> several black office chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 129,
        "problem": "The chair is with what in the back in front of the white board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown rectangular table desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 130,
        "problem": "What color is the chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 131,
        "problem": "Where is the chair on the left? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of white board and behind long brown wooden table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 132,
        "problem": "What is on the wall on the left side of the chair with a backpack on it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> whiteboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 133,
        "problem": "How many chairs face the table with a Starbucks cups on it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0015_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 134,
        "problem": "How many brown arm chairs are stacked against the white wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 8 of them </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 135,
        "problem": "How many black chairs are next to the chairs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 of them </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 136,
        "problem": "What's the color of the chair stacked in a row? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 137,
        "problem": "How many black chairs are located between six brown chairs and a black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 138,
        "problem": "What objects are sitting on the black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 black cushions </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 139,
        "problem": "What color are the chairs next to the couch on right? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 140,
        "problem": "What is the light brown object on wall opposite of black chairs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wood door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 141,
        "problem": "What is to right of two black chairs when facing it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 142,
        "problem": "What color leather chair is next to the black sofa? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 143,
        "problem": "What is to the left of the black chairs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> row of red chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 144,
        "problem": "What is the lamp next to the snack machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tall stand lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 145,
        "problem": "In what part of the building is the lamp located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right next to snack machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 146,
        "problem": "What is next to the snack machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tall floor lamp with black base and white shade </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 147,
        "problem": "What is next to the tall floor lamp? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> snack vending machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 148,
        "problem": "Where is the floor lamp next to the snack machine located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on right side of vending machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 149,
        "problem": "What type of front does the snack machine have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> rectangular glass front </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 150,
        "problem": "What color is the trash container? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> gray </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 151,
        "problem": "What color is the plastic bag in the doorway? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 152,
        "problem": "How many chairs are upside down? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 153,
        "problem": "What color is the chairs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 154,
        "problem": "How many brown chairs are next to a black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 155,
        "problem": "How many brown chairs are next to black couches? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 6 brown chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 156,
        "problem": "Where is the brown chair next to the black couches? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on left side </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 157,
        "problem": "How many black chairs are in the middle between six brown chairs and black couches? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 black chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 158,
        "problem": "What is the black chair next to the brown chairs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black leather chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 159,
        "problem": "How many brown chairs are there? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 6 brown chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 160,
        "problem": "What is on the opposite wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending machine filled with snacks </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 161,
        "problem": "How is the brown chair stacked? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stacked </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 162,
        "problem": "Where is the brown chair from the left? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> against wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 163,
        "problem": "What is the vending machine full of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> snacks </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 164,
        "problem": "What is the position of the brown chair from the left? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stack upside down atop another brown chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 165,
        "problem": "What is in the back right of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending machine full of snacks </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 166,
        "problem": "What is to the left of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending machine full of snacks </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 167,
        "problem": "Where is the trash can located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left of light brown door on floor </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 168,
        "problem": "How many cushions are visible on black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 169,
        "problem": "What is closest to black couch on other side? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 170,
        "problem": "What is left of the stack of red chairs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 171,
        "problem": "What is right of the black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 172,
        "problem": "How many chairs have red chairs stacked on them? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 173,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the vending machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 174,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 175,
        "problem": "What color is the door nearest the trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 176,
        "problem": "What color is the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 177,
        "problem": "What is to the left of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 178,
        "problem": "What is across, from the left side of the vending machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 179,
        "problem": "What is located near a door in a corner of a room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 180,
        "problem": "What has the trash can been placed adjacent to? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 181,
        "problem": "What is to the left of the lamp? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 182,
        "problem": "What sits left of the vending machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 183,
        "problem": "Where are a stack of chairs located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on each side of couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 184,
        "problem": "What color are the chairs on the floor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 185,
        "problem": "Where are the two black chairs located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left of couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 186,
        "problem": "What is in the corner, to the left of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 187,
        "problem": "What is to the right, of the vending machine, in the corner? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 188,
        "problem": "What color leather chair is located on the top right end of the second row? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 189,
        "problem": "Where are the chairs stacked? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner on your left when you walk through door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 190,
        "problem": "How many leather chairs are right of the black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 191,
        "problem": "Where are the brown stacked chairs located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left of 2 black chairs against wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 192,
        "problem": "What color leather chairs are between hanging brown chairs and black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 193,
        "problem": "Where is the red chair on the left? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right of black couch in corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 194,
        "problem": "What color is the chair on the floor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 195,
        "problem": "How many chairs are stacked two high? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 6 chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 196,
        "problem": "What is next to the black snack machine with a white shade on top? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tall floor lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 197,
        "problem": "What color is the door next to the trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 198,
        "problem": "What is on the floor to the right of the vending machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 199,
        "problem": "Which door has a trash can next to it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door across from vending machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 200,
        "problem": "Which door faces the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door with vending machine to its right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 201,
        "problem": "What is inside the trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 202,
        "problem": "What color is the trash can on the floor next to the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> gray </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 203,
        "problem": "The tan wood door is open flat against the wall beside what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 204,
        "problem": "What is close to tan wood door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white cylinder trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 205,
        "problem": "What type of machine is in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 206,
        "problem": "What long piece of furniture can seat multiple people? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 207,
        "problem": "How is the black couch designed to seat 3 people? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 large cushions </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 208,
        "problem": "What is located across from a vending machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 209,
        "problem": "What is the tall tan door located across from? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 210,
        "problem": "What type of machine is by the standing lamp? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 211,
        "problem": "What color is the couch on the left of the vending machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 212,
        "problem": "How many cushions are on the black sofa? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 213,
        "problem": "What type of lamp is beside vending machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> free standing white shade </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 214,
        "problem": "What is to the left of floor lamp? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> vending machine </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 215,
        "problem": "What color shade does the floor lamp have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 216,
        "problem": "What type of lamp is in the corner by the vending machine? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tall floor lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 217,
        "problem": "Where are several chairs located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall opposite door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 218,
        "problem": "What color are the chairs on the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0019_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 219,
        "problem": "What objects are closest to windowsill on shorter desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> keyboard paper towel roll monitor </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 220,
        "problem": "What is sitting closest to windowsill on longer desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> large box with telephone on top </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 221,
        "problem": "The black keyboard is in front of which monitor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> monitor on left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 222,
        "problem": "What is next to the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to tall shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 223,
        "problem": "Where is the cabinet located on the right side of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in middle of northern side of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 224,
        "problem": "Where is the keyboard located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of left side monitor on desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 225,
        "problem": "What is on the right of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 226,
        "problem": "On what color desk is the monitor closest to a whiteboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> light brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 227,
        "problem": "What is the monitor closest to? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> closest to whiteboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 228,
        "problem": "What shape is the monitor shaped like? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> rectangle </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 229,
        "problem": "What is the monitor in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> keyboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 230,
        "problem": "What color is the desk behind the office chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> beige </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 231,
        "problem": "What is the height of the white side table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> about waist height </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 232,
        "problem": "What color is the side table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 233,
        "problem": "On top of the desk is a variety of office supplies such as computer monitors and what else? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white keyboard black keyboard and telephone </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 234,
        "problem": "What is the size of the off white and black monitor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on bigger side </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 235,
        "problem": "Where is the pillow located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left corner of couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 236,
        "problem": "On what side of the wheeled chair is the file cabinet located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right of it </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 237,
        "problem": "What color is the sofa? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 238,
        "problem": "What color is the semi-opened computer case? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 239,
        "problem": "What color is the keyboard on the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 240,
        "problem": "What color is the monitor screen on the shorter curved table closest to window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 241,
        "problem": "What is sitting in front of tall white shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 242,
        "problem": "How many monitors are on shorter curved table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 243,
        "problem": "Where is the monitor sitting? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 244,
        "problem": "What color is the keyboard on the smaller of two desks? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 245,
        "problem": "Where is the white keyboard located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on small desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 246,
        "problem": "The small cabinet sits underneath the window with what on top of it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> book </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 247,
        "problem": "What color is the throw pillow? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> grey colored </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 248,
        "problem": "What color sofa is the throw pillow in? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black sofa </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 249,
        "problem": "What color does the sofa look? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> it looks black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 250,
        "problem": "How many monitors on the desks? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 of them </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 251,
        "problem": "What is the sofa sitting in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> of fan </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 252,
        "problem": "Where is the bookcase placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> under window on left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 253,
        "problem": "What color is the pillow on the left of the black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black and white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 254,
        "problem": "What color is the office chair on wheels? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 255,
        "problem": "Where is the black office chair on wheels located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> around table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 256,
        "problem": "What is the shelf next to? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 257,
        "problem": "What color is the keyboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 258,
        "problem": "The keyboard closest to the door is located on the desk in front of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> monitor </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 259,
        "problem": "Where is the door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> across room opposite windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 260,
        "problem": "What color sticky note is attached to the monitor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> yellow </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 261,
        "problem": "What color shelf is in a corner next to a black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> off white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 262,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the black couch that sits to the right of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 263,
        "problem": "Where is the long tan desk located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> near window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 264,
        "problem": "What is next to the long tan desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 265,
        "problem": "Where is the black short black shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> against wall next to table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 266,
        "problem": "What color is the pillow? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> gray pillow </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 267,
        "problem": "In what corner of a black couch is the gray pillow located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left corner of it </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 268,
        "problem": "Where are the black chairs located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> by desks </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 269,
        "problem": "What color is the sticky note on the monitor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> yellow </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 270,
        "problem": "Where is the white cabinet next to a black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on left side of black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 271,
        "problem": "What color is the couch in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 272,
        "problem": "What color screen is sitting on the desk next to a black framed computer screen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black screen </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 273,
        "problem": "What color is the couch near the shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 274,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 275,
        "problem": "What is the file cabinet under? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 276,
        "problem": "What color is the file cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 277,
        "problem": "What shape is the desk in the middle of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> curved rectangle </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 278,
        "problem": "What beverage is on top of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 279,
        "problem": "What is above the pillow? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> whiteboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 280,
        "problem": "What color couch is the pillow on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 281,
        "problem": "What color is the cube shaped file cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 282,
        "problem": "What color is the couch beneath the whiteboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 283,
        "problem": "What is in front of the couch that is beside the shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> fan </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 284,
        "problem": "What is on the wall in the back left corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 285,
        "problem": "On what side of the room is the shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> front corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 286,
        "problem": "Where is the ottoman located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on right side of black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 287,
        "problem": "What is located to the left of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> gray shelf and black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 288,
        "problem": "What is in front of the shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 289,
        "problem": "Where is the black office chair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of desks </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 290,
        "problem": "What color is the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 291,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is a desk located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> center </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 292,
        "problem": "What shape is the desk on the left side of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> curved </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 293,
        "problem": "What is the telephone on top of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> box </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 294,
        "problem": "What color metal box is on top of a curved table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 295,
        "problem": "The chair is to the right of what table in the center of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 296,
        "problem": "What color is the chair in the center of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 297,
        "problem": "What is in front of the monitor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> headphones cup keyboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 298,
        "problem": "What is located to the right of the shelving? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 299,
        "problem": "On what side of the desk is the telephone located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 300,
        "problem": "Where is the telephone located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on long tan desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 301,
        "problem": "The office chair has casters for what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> casters for wheels </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 302,
        "problem": "Where is the shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner of room up against wall next to brown office desk table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 303,
        "problem": "On what side of the monitor is the shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 304,
        "problem": "What is sitting at the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> office chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 305,
        "problem": "The black chair is in front of what on the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 306,
        "problem": "What is sitting under the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> rectangular brown file cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 307,
        "problem": "What is sitting near a keyboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black rectangular monitor </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 308,
        "problem": "How many empty bottles of coke are behind the black desk chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 1 empty coke bottle </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 309,
        "problem": "Where is the white cabinet in relation to the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of black couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 310,
        "problem": "What is placed on a desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 computer monitors keyboard bottle of water bottle of coke and few other miscellaneous items </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 311,
        "problem": "What is in front of the keyboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ear phones </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 312,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the white work phone? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> box </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 313,
        "problem": "On what part of the table is a table leg located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> end right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 314,
        "problem": "What is sitting next to the computer desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> short cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 315,
        "problem": "What is beside the black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> short rolling cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 316,
        "problem": "What is in front of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> fan </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 317,
        "problem": "What is on the cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> book </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 318,
        "problem": "What is covering the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blinds </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 319,
        "problem": "What color is the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 320,
        "problem": "What color is the filing cabinet on the floor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white filing cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 321,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the couch located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> against wall next to shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 322,
        "problem": "What is in the front corner away from the office desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> large gray bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 323,
        "problem": "What is directly to the right of the white shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 324,
        "problem": "What sits atop the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> monitors most notably </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 325,
        "problem": "What is the keyboard in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of monitor </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 326,
        "problem": "What is located to the left of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 327,
        "problem": "To what side of the chair is the file cabinet located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 328,
        "problem": "What is in the middle of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 329,
        "problem": "What is on the right side of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0025_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 330,
        "problem": "What color is the table against blackboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> light brown top </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 331,
        "problem": "Where are the two different size tables located in room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> side by side </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 332,
        "problem": "What side of long rectangular table is paper? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left edge </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 333,
        "problem": "What color is the chair with wheels? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black office chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 334,
        "problem": "What is at the back of the room where the chalk boards meet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 335,
        "problem": "How many chalk boards are there? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 336,
        "problem": "How long is the table in front of the chalk board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> medium </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 337,
        "problem": "The table in front of the chalk board is as long as what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 338,
        "problem": "How many chairs does the table in front of the chalk board have around it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 339,
        "problem": "What is the third chair under the chalk board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown metal chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 340,
        "problem": "What is the color of the chair closest to the first book shelf closest to the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 341,
        "problem": "What chair is right of the blackboard that is closest to the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 342,
        "problem": "Which book shelf from the left is shorter than all the rest? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> by chalkboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 343,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 344,
        "problem": "Where is the small book shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chalkboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 345,
        "problem": "What is at the end of the chalk board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 346,
        "problem": "What color is the chair on the right of the chalk board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown easy chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 347,
        "problem": "Where is the brown chair on the chalk board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner between chalkboards </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 348,
        "problem": "On what side of the door is the book shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left when you walk in through it </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 349,
        "problem": "What is in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> reclining armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 350,
        "problem": "Where is the small bookshelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right corner under window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 351,
        "problem": "What color blinds are on the window behind the bookshelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 352,
        "problem": "What is in the corner by windows? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> book shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 353,
        "problem": "What can be seen on chalk board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> writing </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 354,
        "problem": "What type of chair is in the corner of the blackboards? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 355,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the brown armchair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 356,
        "problem": "What is around the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> doorframe </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 357,
        "problem": "What color chair is the tan chair next to? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 358,
        "problem": "What is next to a desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown armchair and blue office chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 359,
        "problem": "How many chairs are at the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 office chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 360,
        "problem": "What is next to the chalkboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> arm chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 361,
        "problem": "What is on the bookshelf next to the chalkboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> book shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 362,
        "problem": "How many shelfs are on the book shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 363,
        "problem": "What is behind the armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blackboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 364,
        "problem": "What is beneath the clock? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blackboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 365,
        "problem": "What is behind the small bookshelf on the left side of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 366,
        "problem": "Where is the broad brown plain table placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in center </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 367,
        "problem": "What is rotatable? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 368,
        "problem": "Where is the rolling chair kept from the corner chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 369,
        "problem": "What color is the chair in the corner of one side of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 370,
        "problem": "What type of chair is close to the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 371,
        "problem": "How close to the wall is the chair with arms? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> very </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 372,
        "problem": "What color is the tabletop with no arms? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 373,
        "problem": "What color is the cushion sofa in? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 374,
        "problem": "Where is the cushion sofa located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> near wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 375,
        "problem": "What type of table is kept at the corner of the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 376,
        "problem": "Where is a long table kept? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at corner of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 377,
        "problem": "What color is the chair near the center of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 378,
        "problem": "What does the chair face? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 379,
        "problem": "Where are the windows in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 380,
        "problem": "What color recliner is in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 381,
        "problem": "Where is the brown recliner? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner of walls with blackboards </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 382,
        "problem": "What color are the tables near the center of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown and tan </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 383,
        "problem": "What is at the right end of a table with windows directly to its right? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bag sitting vaguely close to it </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 384,
        "problem": "Where is the light brown chair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 385,
        "problem": "What color office chair is placed in a table lying parallel to a long green board on the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 386,
        "problem": "Where is the bookshelf placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall to left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 387,
        "problem": "How many green boards do the adjacent walls have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 388,
        "problem": "What color is the chair on the left hand side of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 389,
        "problem": "What color leather chair is located in the aisle in the middle of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 390,
        "problem": "Where is the brown leather armchair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner between 2 blackboards </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 391,
        "problem": "What color chair is to the left of light colored table under blackboard? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 392,
        "problem": "On what side of the room is the brown leather armchair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> corner between 2 blackboards by longest wood table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 393,
        "problem": "What is on top of the bookcase? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> books </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 394,
        "problem": "Where is the bookcase located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> near window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 395,
        "problem": "What is on the bookshelf next to the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> books </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 396,
        "problem": "Where is the tall bookshelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> near blackboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 397,
        "problem": "What color is the chair with wheels located at a desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 398,
        "problem": "The chair on the left of a desk is closest to what corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> entrance </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 399,
        "problem": "What is the blue chair with 4 wooden legs under? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 400,
        "problem": "Where is the blue chair facing away from you when you enter the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> under table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 401,
        "problem": "What kind of shelving is in the right hand most corner next to the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 402,
        "problem": "In which corner of the room is the bookcase located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 403,
        "problem": "Which table has the office chair with plastic wheels? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back left table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 404,
        "problem": "What color is the chair at the desk farthest away from the entrance? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 405,
        "problem": "In what color is the office chair facing away from you? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 406,
        "problem": "What are there around the room facing the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 407,
        "problem": "What is the only chair in the middle of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> office chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 408,
        "problem": "What is on the wall to the right of the armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blackboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 409,
        "problem": "Where is the chair located on the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> both sides </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 410,
        "problem": "How is the black chair removed from the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> diagonally </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 411,
        "problem": "What type of table is above the boxes? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> long table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 412,
        "problem": "The long table is above what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> some boxes </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 413,
        "problem": "Where is the brown bookshelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner to left of white table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 414,
        "problem": "What kind of table is under the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> long light brown wooden rectangular </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 415,
        "problem": "Where is the long table located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> underneath 3 windows against wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 416,
        "problem": "What color is the chair that is pushed away from table in center row? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 417,
        "problem": "The long table is across from what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> smaller rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 418,
        "problem": "Where is the long table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 419,
        "problem": "What is the black chair in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in center of room pushed out from desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 420,
        "problem": "Where is the tan chair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at light brown rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 421,
        "problem": "Where is the brown chair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at dark brown rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 422,
        "problem": "What color chair is next to the blue chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 423,
        "problem": "The rectangular table is in front of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> long rectangular green blackboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 424,
        "problem": "How is the table placed to the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> up against wall under green blackboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 425,
        "problem": "Where can a single seat sofa be seen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 426,
        "problem": "What two chairs are in front of blackboard behind table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown grey chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 427,
        "problem": "What is the chair that is in left center row tucked under? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> long brown table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 428,
        "problem": "What kind of wheels does the chair have that sits at corner of a table with long rectangular table across from it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black rolling </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 429,
        "problem": "What is on the wooden table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bag </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 430,
        "problem": "Along with a stapler, what else is on the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bag </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 431,
        "problem": "What is tucked under the table on both of its long sides? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 432,
        "problem": "What is next to the bookshelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 433,
        "problem": "What color is the chair on the left? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 434,
        "problem": "How many legs does the chair have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 435,
        "problem": "What color are the chairs closest to the tallest bookshelves? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 436,
        "problem": "How many bookshelves can be seen in the scene? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 437,
        "problem": "How many blackboards are in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 438,
        "problem": "What is the table on the right in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> long blackboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 439,
        "problem": "What color is the table on the right in front of the book cases? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 440,
        "problem": "What is the table in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 441,
        "problem": "How many chairs are pushed under the chalk board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 442,
        "problem": "What color is the table in front of a chalk board? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 443,
        "problem": "Where is the auburn chair located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner between 2 chalkboards </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 444,
        "problem": "What is in front of the brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blackboard </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 445,
        "problem": "What is behind the brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> book shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 446,
        "problem": "Where is the rectangular table located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> middle of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 447,
        "problem": "The long table is below what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 448,
        "problem": "Where is the chair with arms located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below blackboard against wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 449,
        "problem": "The blue office chair is pushed away from what object? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> rectangular table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0030_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 450,
        "problem": "What does it do? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> flush toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 451,
        "problem": "Where is the button located on the top side of the toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above white toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 452,
        "problem": "What is at the end of the hallway? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black rectangular door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 453,
        "problem": "What color sign is on the black door at the end of the hallway? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red and white sign </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 454,
        "problem": "What is the tall brown cabinet next to? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue plaid curtains </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 455,
        "problem": "What color is the cabinet next to the blue plaid curtains? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 456,
        "problem": "What is hanging between the sink and the toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> towel </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 457,
        "problem": "Where is the blue towel hanging? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> between toilet and sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 458,
        "problem": "Where is the blue door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> entrance </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 459,
        "problem": "What color sign is on the blue door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red and white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 460,
        "problem": "What is the object behind 2 pairs of shoes? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 461,
        "problem": "How many pairs of shoes is the table behind? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 462,
        "problem": "Where is the toilet located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to towel under toilet paper </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 463,
        "problem": "What is the tall brown wooden cabinet called? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wardrobe </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 464,
        "problem": "What color curtains are on the right of the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> green and blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 465,
        "problem": "What is the chair in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> light brown desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 466,
        "problem": "A blue and brown chair is in front of a desk with what on it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> several objects laptop stand black laptop </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 467,
        "problem": "What color is the wooden nightstand? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> light brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 468,
        "problem": "What kind of desk is the computer located on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small brown desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 469,
        "problem": "What is on the desk in front of the blue and brown chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> computer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 470,
        "problem": "What is positioned above the toilet and on the left of the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ledge </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 471,
        "problem": "What is above the toilet flush button? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white ledge </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 472,
        "problem": "What color is the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 473,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue towel </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 474,
        "problem": "What color is the bathtub on the far right of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 475,
        "problem": "On what side of the room is a white bathtub with a white shower curtain? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 476,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the bathtub? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 477,
        "problem": "What color pillow is positioned at the head of a bed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> while pillow </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 478,
        "problem": "What is underneath the white pillow? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue bed sheets </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 479,
        "problem": "What is above the toilet to flush the toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> flushing button </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 480,
        "problem": "What color is the towel to the right of the toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 481,
        "problem": "What color is the mat beneath the toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 482,
        "problem": "What color is the shower curtain? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 483,
        "problem": "What is hanging in the corner between the cabinets and the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> curtains </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 484,
        "problem": "Where is the tv located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> between picture and wardrobe </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 485,
        "problem": "What is to the left of the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 486,
        "problem": "What part of a white toilet is opened? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> cover seat </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 487,
        "problem": "What is at the foot of the bed with two teirs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table end shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 488,
        "problem": "How many teirs are on the table end shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 tiers </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 489,
        "problem": "What color entry door is in front of the toliet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 490,
        "problem": "Where is the white entry door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 491,
        "problem": "What is located above the open toilet seat? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> toilet flush button </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 492,
        "problem": "Where is the backpack located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right of blue and brown chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 493,
        "problem": "What color is the wardrobe in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 494,
        "problem": "How many doors does the brown wardrobe have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 doors </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 495,
        "problem": "What color curtains are next to the wardrobe? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue green </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 496,
        "problem": "To what side of the sink is the white shower curtain located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 497,
        "problem": "What color is the tv above the night stand? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 498,
        "problem": "The black tv is hung above what color night stand? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown wooden color </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 499,
        "problem": "What is suspended on the wall between the tall brown cabinet and the wall to the right of the tv? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> rectangular picture </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 500,
        "problem": "What is under the tv on the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown wooden nightstand </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 501,
        "problem": "What color is the bathroom door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 502,
        "problem": "What color is the apartment door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 503,
        "problem": "What is the front door to the apartment? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 504,
        "problem": "What color is the front door to the apartment? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 505,
        "problem": "The nightstand is in-between what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> between bed and wardrobe </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 506,
        "problem": "What color is the bathtub in the bathroom? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 507,
        "problem": "What is located to the left of the bathtub? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shower curtain </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 508,
        "problem": "Where is the bathtub located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind shower curtain inside bathroom </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 509,
        "problem": "Where is the bathtub located in the bathroom? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of doorframe and light switch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 510,
        "problem": "What is in front of the toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 511,
        "problem": "What is on top of the bathtub? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shower curtain </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 512,
        "problem": "Where is the bathtub positioned? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 513,
        "problem": "How far from the window curtains is the chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> few inches from curtains </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 514,
        "problem": "Where is the white bathtub located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 515,
        "problem": "What color is the tv above a bed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 516,
        "problem": "What is the black tv above? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bed </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 517,
        "problem": "What type of sink is next to a toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 518,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the white sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shower curtain </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 519,
        "problem": "Where is the bed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on corner to left of bathroom </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 520,
        "problem": "What color is the towel between the toilet and the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 521,
        "problem": "What color chair is next to the tan desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 522,
        "problem": "What color is the bed in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 523,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the white bed located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 524,
        "problem": "On what side of the bed is the pillow located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right side when facing bed </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 525,
        "problem": "Where is the desk located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> adjacent wall to left of curtains </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 526,
        "problem": "What electronic device is sitting atop the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black laptop </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 527,
        "problem": "How is the laptop located on top of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in center of desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 528,
        "problem": "What is the laptop centered on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown wooden desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 529,
        "problem": "What is located to the right of the toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 530,
        "problem": "Where is the curtain located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left of wardrobe </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 531,
        "problem": "What color sink is near the shower curtain? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 532,
        "problem": "How many legs does the arm chair have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 533,
        "problem": "What type of chair has four legs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue cushioned chair light brown wood </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 534,
        "problem": "Where is the wooden chair with blue cushion placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of wood desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 535,
        "problem": "Where is the toilet flush button by the toilet basin? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above toilet lid </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 536,
        "problem": "What is above the bed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> picture </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 537,
        "problem": "What color is the main door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 538,
        "problem": "What is in front of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 539,
        "problem": "Where has the white door been swung into? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bathroom </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 540,
        "problem": "What is on the bed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue blanket white blanket pillow </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 541,
        "problem": "Where is the pillow? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on bed </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 542,
        "problem": "How is the blue bath towel hung? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall next to sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 543,
        "problem": "What color is the chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown and blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 544,
        "problem": "Where is the blue and brown chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 545,
        "problem": "What color sink is attached to the wall of the bathroom? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> off white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 546,
        "problem": "Where is the off-white sink located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bathroom </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 547,
        "problem": "What color is the entry door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 548,
        "problem": "Where is the off-white door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in hallway </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 549,
        "problem": "What color is the pillow on the bed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 550,
        "problem": "Where is the off-white pillow on the bed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at head of bed </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 551,
        "problem": "What is above the toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> button </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 552,
        "problem": "Where is the white toilet flush button located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on top of toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 553,
        "problem": "What color laptop sits on top of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 554,
        "problem": "What is covering the windows? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> curtains </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 555,
        "problem": "What is hanging on the wall to the left of the windows? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> lamp </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 556,
        "problem": "What color is the chair cushion? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 557,
        "problem": "What can be seen hanging by the bathtub? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white shower curtain </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 558,
        "problem": "What color is the surface of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> green </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 559,
        "problem": "How many pairs of shoes can be seen lying in front of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 pairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0046_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 560,
        "problem": "Where is the laptop located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on top of desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 561,
        "problem": "Where is the stool located in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 562,
        "problem": "What is on top of the stool? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> toolbox </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 563,
        "problem": "The chair has its back to what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 564,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the chair next to the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> nearest brown door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 565,
        "problem": "What is on the ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> backpacks and tissue box </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 566,
        "problem": "What is a box of on the ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tissue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 567,
        "problem": "What type of box is on the ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tissue box </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 568,
        "problem": "What color shelf is next to the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 569,
        "problem": "What is next to the white shelf in the wall on top of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 570,
        "problem": "What color is the shelf on the breaker box? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 571,
        "problem": "The shelf is up against what to the left of the dark grey breaker box? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 572,
        "problem": "What is on the brown ottoman in front of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> backpacks and tissue box </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 573,
        "problem": "The backpack is to the right of a box of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tissues </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 574,
        "problem": "What is in front of the shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> laptop </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 575,
        "problem": "What is the shelf above against the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 576,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 577,
        "problem": "What is on the left side of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 578,
        "problem": "What is on the wall near the armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 579,
        "problem": "What is on the left wall of the house? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 580,
        "problem": "How is the couch sitting to the windows? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of windows </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 581,
        "problem": "What color is the printer on the right side of a desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 582,
        "problem": "The printer is closest to what on the right? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 583,
        "problem": "What is in front of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 584,
        "problem": "Where is the laptop sitting? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 585,
        "problem": "Where are the two doors located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> near arm chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 586,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the brown piano located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> corner of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 587,
        "problem": "Where is the red toolbox located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right of piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 588,
        "problem": "What color is the piano bench in front of the piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 589,
        "problem": "Where is the brown piano bench located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 590,
        "problem": "What is the white tissue box sitting between? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> backpacks </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 591,
        "problem": "Where is the silver and white desk located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> near brown door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 592,
        "problem": "Where is the brown door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> near armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 593,
        "problem": "What type of backpack is in front of a couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 594,
        "problem": "What is the black backpack in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 595,
        "problem": "What is the color of the laptop that is on a desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 596,
        "problem": "Where is the ray laptop located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 597,
        "problem": "What is the black backpack on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 598,
        "problem": "Where is the brown couch located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 599,
        "problem": "The brown armchair is across from what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 600,
        "problem": "What is in front of the brown couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 601,
        "problem": "What is next to the brown door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 602,
        "problem": "What is near the brown armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 603,
        "problem": "What is next to the toolbox? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 604,
        "problem": "The silver laptop is across from what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 605,
        "problem": "What is in front of the brown door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 606,
        "problem": "What is the backpack on top of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 607,
        "problem": "What is next to the brown piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tool boxes </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 608,
        "problem": "What is next to the brown couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 609,
        "problem": "What color is the armchair next to the laptop? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 610,
        "problem": "What is next to the tool boxes? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 611,
        "problem": "What is next to the shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 612,
        "problem": "What color toolbox is in front of a red toolbox? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> green </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 613,
        "problem": "What color is the toolbox behind the blue toolbox? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 614,
        "problem": "What is the armchair facing? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 615,
        "problem": "What is located to the right of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> piano bench </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 616,
        "problem": "What color is the armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 617,
        "problem": "What is located on the floor to the left of the piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> toolbox </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 618,
        "problem": "How many boxes does the stool have on top of it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 619,
        "problem": "The backpack is sitting on top of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 620,
        "problem": "The backpack is to what side of the piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 621,
        "problem": "What is in front of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 622,
        "problem": "What is located on top of the ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> backpack </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 623,
        "problem": "What is the tissue box sitting between on top of the ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> backpack </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 624,
        "problem": "Where is the grey printer located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right of laptop </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 625,
        "problem": "What color is the piano to the right of the double doors? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 626,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue and red toolboxes </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 627,
        "problem": "What color leather chair is in front of the grey desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 628,
        "problem": "What is sitting in front of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 629,
        "problem": "What is in front of the glass double doors? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 630,
        "problem": "The floral printed chair is to the left of what color desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 631,
        "problem": "What is the black knapsack resting on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 632,
        "problem": "Where is the sofa located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 633,
        "problem": "What color piano is in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 634,
        "problem": "What does the black knapsack rest on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 635,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the black knapsack? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tissue box </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 636,
        "problem": "What kind of doors are in front of the knapsack? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown wooden doors </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 637,
        "problem": "What color is the laptop computer on the left edge of a messy desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 638,
        "problem": "What is the laptop sitting on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 639,
        "problem": "What is sitting near the right side of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> piano bench </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 640,
        "problem": "What color is the piano on the left of the ottomon? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 641,
        "problem": "What sits on the right edge of a brown leather ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> backpack </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 642,
        "problem": "Along with a black backsack, what is on the right edge of the brown leather ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small black backpack </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 643,
        "problem": "What kind of table is underneath the black backsack? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 644,
        "problem": "How many doors are in the back? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 645,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 646,
        "problem": "What is to the left of a desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 647,
        "problem": "What type of desk sits just ahead of a wall that has glass doors in it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 648,
        "problem": "What is space between the desk and the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 649,
        "problem": "What does the brown leather ottoman sit in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 650,
        "problem": "What sits in front of a matching sofa to its right? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 651,
        "problem": "What is in a corner of the ottomon? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> backpack </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 652,
        "problem": "What is in front of the piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> piano bench </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 653,
        "problem": "What is the printer sitting on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 654,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the toobox? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 655,
        "problem": "What is the toolbox against? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 656,
        "problem": "Where is the brown ottoman located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 657,
        "problem": "What is underneath the brown stool? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 658,
        "problem": "What is next to the laptop? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> laptop </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 659,
        "problem": "The laptop is on a desk facing what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 660,
        "problem": "What is the blue toolbox in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red tool box </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 661,
        "problem": "What is the tool box near? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> piano </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 662,
        "problem": "What is in the corner of the room to the right of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 663,
        "problem": "What color is the tool boxes to the left of the piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red green </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 664,
        "problem": "What color is the tool box to the left of the piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red green </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 665,
        "problem": "Where is the piano located in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bottom right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 666,
        "problem": "What color toolbox is to the right of the piano? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> green red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 667,
        "problem": "The piano is to the right of a blue toolbox and what else on the floor? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red toolbox </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 668,
        "problem": "What color leather reclining chair is in front of a grey desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 669,
        "problem": "What is in front of the arm chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 670,
        "problem": "What color is the desk in front of a brown chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 671,
        "problem": "How many laptops are on top of the desk? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 672,
        "problem": "The rectangular tissue box is on what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown rectangular ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 673,
        "problem": "What is next to the brown door on the left? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white wooden desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 674,
        "problem": "The brown door is to what side of the window with white curtain? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 675,
        "problem": "What is next to the black backpack? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tissue box </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 676,
        "problem": "Where is the printer located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 677,
        "problem": "Where is the chair with arms located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of desk </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0050_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 678,
        "problem": "What color is the cabinet next to the fridge? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 679,
        "problem": "Where is the dark brown wooden cabinet placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below kitchen counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 680,
        "problem": "What color is the cabinet above the fridge? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> grey </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 681,
        "problem": "Where is the brown wooden cabinet placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left of fridge </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 682,
        "problem": "What color is the refrigerator in the kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 683,
        "problem": "Where is a silver color refrigerator located in the kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 684,
        "problem": "What color table is placed against the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> light brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 685,
        "problem": "The light wood color table is to the left of what on the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 686,
        "problem": "What is next to the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 687,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the light wood color table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 688,
        "problem": "On what color table is a microwave placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 689,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the light wood colored table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 690,
        "problem": "What is on the left of the refrigerator? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> kitchen cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 691,
        "problem": "What color is the counter top on the fridge? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 692,
        "problem": "What kind of sink is on the black counter top? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stainless steel </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 693,
        "problem": "What kind of microwave is in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> stainless steel </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 694,
        "problem": "How many chairs are on the left side of the microwave? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 1 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 695,
        "problem": "What type of fridge is in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> freezer on top refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 696,
        "problem": "What is directly beside the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 697,
        "problem": "What type of small appliance is on the wooden table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> microwave </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 698,
        "problem": "What is the microwave on? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 699,
        "problem": "What color is the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 700,
        "problem": "What kind of fridge is on the left of the red door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 701,
        "problem": "What color is the kitchen island? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> grey silver </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 702,
        "problem": "What kind of fridge is in front of the dark kitchen island? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> freezer on top </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 703,
        "problem": "What color is the door in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 704,
        "problem": "On what side of the room is the red door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right side of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 705,
        "problem": "What color is the chair on the left side of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 706,
        "problem": "What does the brown wooden chair lack? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> arms </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 707,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the fridge? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 708,
        "problem": "What kind of fridge is underneath the cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 709,
        "problem": "Where is the fridge located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to kitchen cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 710,
        "problem": "What color is the entry door in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 711,
        "problem": "What type of fridge is on the left of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> freezer on top </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 712,
        "problem": "What is in the room that has a sink on its right side and a coffee pot on its left side? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> kitchen counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 713,
        "problem": "What is on the right side of the counter top? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 714,
        "problem": "What is in the room that has two chairs pulled up to it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> kitchen island </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 715,
        "problem": "What is the countertop with 2 chairs pulled up to it called? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> kitchen island </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 716,
        "problem": "What color is the microwave? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 717,
        "problem": "Where does the silver microwave set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 718,
        "problem": "How does the table set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 719,
        "problem": "What does the black kitchen cabinet set next to? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> fridge </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 720,
        "problem": "What is in the center of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> kitchen island </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 721,
        "problem": "Where does a kitchen cabinet set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> beneath kitchen counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 722,
        "problem": "Where is the black kitchen cabinet affixed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> beneath kitchen counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 723,
        "problem": "What color is the kitchen counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> grey </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 724,
        "problem": "Where does the black kitchen counter set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> middle of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 725,
        "problem": "Where does the brown chair set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of square table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 726,
        "problem": "What color is the door that opens into the kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 727,
        "problem": "What is the brown chair next to? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 728,
        "problem": "What color is the kitchen cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 729,
        "problem": "Where is the kitchen cabinet located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of fridge </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 730,
        "problem": "The kitchen cabinet is located to the left of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> fridge </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 731,
        "problem": "What is located to the left of the red door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> fridge </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 732,
        "problem": "On what side of the kitchen is the refrigerator located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 733,
        "problem": "The chair is located to the left of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 734,
        "problem": "Where is the kitchen counter located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above kitchen cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 735,
        "problem": "The kitchen counter is located to the left of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 736,
        "problem": "What is located to the right of the kitchen counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 737,
        "problem": "On what side of the red door is the refrigerator located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 738,
        "problem": "What color is the eating table in the middle of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> gray </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 739,
        "problem": "Where is the gray eating table placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> middle of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 740,
        "problem": "What color is the wooden table on the side of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 741,
        "problem": "Where is the beige wooden table placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> side of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 742,
        "problem": "What color is the chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 743,
        "problem": "Where is the beige wooden chair placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 744,
        "problem": "Where does the brown table set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> against wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 745,
        "problem": "What is on top of the brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> microwave </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 746,
        "problem": "Where does the microwave set? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 747,
        "problem": "What does the black kitchen cabinet set by? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> refrigerator </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0063_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 748,
        "problem": "What type of loveseat is in a library? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 749,
        "problem": "Where would the tall book shelf be if you were sitting in the loveseat? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 750,
        "problem": "What is the purpose of a black leather loveseat in a library? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to sit in </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 751,
        "problem": "What color is the shelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 752,
        "problem": "Where are the squares of the shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 753,
        "problem": "What color is the arm chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 754,
        "problem": "What is the brown arm chair made of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> leather </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 755,
        "problem": "What color leather is the armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 756,
        "problem": "Where is the brown leather armchair placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> around coffee table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 757,
        "problem": "What color is the wooden square table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> light brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 758,
        "problem": "Where is the brown wooden square table placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of chair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 759,
        "problem": "What is on the table on the right side of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> microwave </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 760,
        "problem": "Where is the shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 761,
        "problem": "The coffee table is to the left of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 762,
        "problem": "The coffee table is to the right of what armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 763,
        "problem": "Where is the coffee table located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 764,
        "problem": "What is behind the coffee table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 765,
        "problem": "What is in front of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 766,
        "problem": "What are on the walls behind and to the right of the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 767,
        "problem": "What is directly behind the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 768,
        "problem": "On what side of the room is a bookshelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right and front </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 769,
        "problem": "Where is the short bookshelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 770,
        "problem": "How many shelves does the short bookshelf have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 4 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 771,
        "problem": "The armchair is located to what side of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 772,
        "problem": "What has it's back against an identical object? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 773,
        "problem": "What is the armchair facing? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 774,
        "problem": "What is in the background of the armchair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 775,
        "problem": "What is next to a black couch in a room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 776,
        "problem": "How is the bookshelf in a room connected to another bookcase on the back wall of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 777,
        "problem": "What color coffee table is in the center of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 778,
        "problem": "What is in the center of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> arm chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 779,
        "problem": "The black couch is in front of what bookcase? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 780,
        "problem": "The couch is in front of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 781,
        "problem": "What is directly behind another brown chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> armchair </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 782,
        "problem": "What is in front of the brown chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 783,
        "problem": "What color table is in the center of two black couches? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 784,
        "problem": "Are the couches adjacent or opposite each other? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> opposite </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 785,
        "problem": "What is between the coffee tables? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> arm chairs </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 786,
        "problem": "The brown arm chair sets a little away from what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee tables </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 787,
        "problem": "The black couch sets quite close to what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 788,
        "problem": "The brown arm chair faces toward what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown coffee table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 789,
        "problem": "On what side of the room is the bookshelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 790,
        "problem": "Where are the bookshelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 791,
        "problem": "Where is the bookshelf at the far end of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right of door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 792,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the coffee table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 793,
        "problem": "How many armchairs are there? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 794,
        "problem": "Where is the bookshelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 795,
        "problem": "Where is the bookshelf behind the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 796,
        "problem": "What is the black couch facing? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee tables </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 797,
        "problem": "What is in front of the black couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 798,
        "problem": "What kind of shelf is next to some brown armchairs? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> book shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 799,
        "problem": "What is closest to the bookshelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 800,
        "problem": "What color are the chairs around the brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 801,
        "problem": "What color are the couches around the brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 802,
        "problem": "What is the bookhelf behind? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 803,
        "problem": "What is the length of the bookcase in the back? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> short </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 804,
        "problem": "Where does the bookshelf run lengthwise? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> along wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 805,
        "problem": "What is the brown armchair facing? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> coffee table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 806,
        "problem": "What color leather chair is in a library? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 807,
        "problem": "Where would the long short bookshelf be if you were sitting in a tan leather chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 808,
        "problem": "What would be on your right if you were sitting in the black loveseat facing the end table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 809,
        "problem": "On what side of the loveseat would you find a long, short bookshelf? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 810,
        "problem": "What is in the back of the loveseat? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bookshelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0064_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 811,
        "problem": "What is behind the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 812,
        "problem": "Where is the black trash can located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 813,
        "problem": "What color is a door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 814,
        "problem": "Where is the brown door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to copier </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 815,
        "problem": "What type of machine is in front of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> copier </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 816,
        "problem": "What is the white machine in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 817,
        "problem": "What color is the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 818,
        "problem": "What color is the open door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 819,
        "problem": "What is right in front of the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 820,
        "problem": "What is in the back of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shelves </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 821,
        "problem": "What color does the cabinet in the back of the room appear to be? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 822,
        "problem": "What color is the trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 823,
        "problem": "What is next to the trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> copier </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 824,
        "problem": "What color is the counter on the back of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> gray </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 825,
        "problem": "Where is the counter located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 826,
        "problem": "Where is the printer located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 827,
        "problem": "What type of door is in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wooden </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 828,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the wooden door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 829,
        "problem": "On what wall is the copier mounted? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 830,
        "problem": "What type of window is above the counter on the right side? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small rectangular </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 831,
        "problem": "Where is the window on the right side? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 832,
        "problem": "On what type of surface is the printer located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 833,
        "problem": "What is in the back of the room against the back wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 834,
        "problem": "What color does the trash can appear to be? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 835,
        "problem": "What color is the copier? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> grey </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 836,
        "problem": "What type of copier is the copier on the right side of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> large grey office </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 837,
        "problem": "On what side of the room is the copier located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 838,
        "problem": "What color is the printer? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 839,
        "problem": "On what side of the counter in the back of the room is the printer located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> center </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 840,
        "problem": "Where are the cabinets located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 841,
        "problem": "On what side of the counter is the printer located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> far side </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 842,
        "problem": "What is in an office that holds the printer and files? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 843,
        "problem": "Where is the counter in an office that holds the printer and files? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 844,
        "problem": "What color printer is sitting on the counter in the office? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 845,
        "problem": "Where is the black printer sitting on the counter in the office? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 846,
        "problem": "On what side of the room is the window in the office located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 847,
        "problem": "Where is the window in the office located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> far side of room </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 848,
        "problem": "What is the office printer sitting on the far back against the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 849,
        "problem": "Where is the office printer in the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 850,
        "problem": "What kind of shelves are on the far wall when you walk into a room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wall mounted </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 851,
        "problem": "Where are the office shelves located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 852,
        "problem": "Where is the black copier located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> next to trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 853,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the brown door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 854,
        "problem": "What is to the left of a copier? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 855,
        "problem": "What type of cabinet is at the end of the room against a wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> long white cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 856,
        "problem": "Where is the white cabinet located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below countertop </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 857,
        "problem": "What color counter is on top of a white cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 858,
        "problem": "What is the black counter on top of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 859,
        "problem": "What type of counter is below a window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 860,
        "problem": "Where is the black counter located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above white cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 861,
        "problem": "What type of window is above a black counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small rectangular </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 862,
        "problem": "What is below the window with blinds? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 863,
        "problem": "What color cabinet is below a counter top? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 864,
        "problem": "What is located in front of the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 865,
        "problem": "Where is the square printer located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> beside shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 866,
        "problem": "The large copier is to the right of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 867,
        "problem": "What kind of cabinet is the copier in front of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> long and white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 868,
        "problem": "What is the white cabinet facing? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> copier </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 869,
        "problem": "What type of shelf is above a cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 shelf cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 870,
        "problem": "Where is the wall-mounted shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 871,
        "problem": "What is on the wood floor and against the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trashcan </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 872,
        "problem": "What is placed on the wooden floor against the wall on the left? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 873,
        "problem": "What appears just after the trashcan? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> copier </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 874,
        "problem": "What has been placed against the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 875,
        "problem": "To the left of the copier is what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 876,
        "problem": "What is the shelf attached to above the counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 877,
        "problem": "The shelf is to the left of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 878,
        "problem": "What is placed against the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 879,
        "problem": "To the right of the trash can is what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 880,
        "problem": "Where is a printer placed? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 881,
        "problem": "What is located slightly to the left of the printer? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> shelf </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 882,
        "problem": "Where is the shelf located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 883,
        "problem": "What wall is the window in? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left wall far side </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 884,
        "problem": "What is the copier sitting to the right of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 885,
        "problem": "What are to the right of the copier? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 886,
        "problem": "What is the only window in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right of shelves </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 887,
        "problem": "The built-in shelf is the left of the only what in the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> copier </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 888,
        "problem": "What type of window is in the corner of the room above the counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 paned window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 889,
        "problem": "Where is the window in the corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> back right corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 890,
        "problem": "In what part of the room is the window above the counter located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 891,
        "problem": "Where is the window above the counter at the back of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 892,
        "problem": "Where is the window located in the back of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in corner </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 893,
        "problem": "What type of cabinet is located below the window in a kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white cabinet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 894,
        "problem": "Where is the lower white cabinet located in a kitchen? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 895,
        "problem": "Where is the small trash can located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> between doors </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 896,
        "problem": "What is sitting on a wooden table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> printer </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 897,
        "problem": "Where does the copier sit from the window and cabinet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below window </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 898,
        "problem": "What color is the door that is located beside a table with a copier on it? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> brown </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 899,
        "problem": "What is on the table next to the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> copier </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 900,
        "problem": "What type of trash can is sitting between the stove and the stove? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> black trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 901,
        "problem": "Where is the trash can sitting? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> between doors </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0077_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 902,
        "problem": "What is under a round table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 903,
        "problem": "What is the red squared chair under? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 904,
        "problem": "What is next to a red squared chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 905,
        "problem": "What type of chair is next to the round brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 906,
        "problem": "What kind of table is right behind a long black chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ound table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 907,
        "problem": "What is right behind the round brown table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 908,
        "problem": "What color is the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 909,
        "problem": "What is the dark blue couch right behind? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 910,
        "problem": "What color chair is next to a long blue couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 911,
        "problem": "What color couch is next to the small red chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 912,
        "problem": "What is the shape of the small red chair? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> square </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 913,
        "problem": "What color is the booth style couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 914,
        "problem": "Where is the couch located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind tables </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 915,
        "problem": "What is on the ground to the left of the round table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 916,
        "problem": "Where is the ottoman located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> near small round table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 917,
        "problem": "What color is the ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 918,
        "problem": "Where is the ottoman located on the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> at right end </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 919,
        "problem": "What color is the booth? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 920,
        "problem": "What color is the vinyl booth couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 921,
        "problem": "Where is the booth couch located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind round tables </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 922,
        "problem": "What is up against a red wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> booths </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 923,
        "problem": "How many wooden tables are on either side of the blue couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 924,
        "problem": "What color is the cube shaped footrest? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 925,
        "problem": "What is the footrest near the end of? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 926,
        "problem": "What color couch is next to the footrest? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 927,
        "problem": "What shape is the wooden table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> round </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 928,
        "problem": "What color couch is in front of the wooden table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 929,
        "problem": "What color is the cube-shaped footrest? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 930,
        "problem": "The footrest is in front of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 931,
        "problem": "Where is the footrest located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below tables </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 932,
        "problem": "What shape is the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> round </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 933,
        "problem": "What color stool is beside the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 934,
        "problem": "What is on the right side of the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 935,
        "problem": "What color stool does the first small circular table not have? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 936,
        "problem": "What color is the bench? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 937,
        "problem": "What color is the back of the bench? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> blue and white stripes </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 938,
        "problem": "Where is the small round table located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of couches </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 939,
        "problem": "How many small round tables are in front of the bend between the couches? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 1 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 940,
        "problem": "How many small round tables are there? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 3 </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 941,
        "problem": "What color is the bench seat? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 942,
        "problem": "What is the blue couch behind? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> round tables </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 943,
        "problem": "What color cushion is next to the round table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> red </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 944,
        "problem": "What color couch is next to a red cushion? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> dark blue </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 945,
        "problem": "What is next to the blue couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> round table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 946,
        "problem": "What is next to a round table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 947,
        "problem": "What is next to the ottoman? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> round table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 948,
        "problem": "What is next to the little round table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 949,
        "problem": "The large couch is next to what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small round table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 950,
        "problem": "What is against the wall by the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> long couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 951,
        "problem": "What is on the right by the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small round table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 952,
        "problem": "The small round table is on the right by what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 953,
        "problem": "What is next to the table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 954,
        "problem": "Where is the square ottoman located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 955,
        "problem": "What is by the round table? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 956,
        "problem": "The couch corner is by what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 957,
        "problem": "What is by the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 958,
        "problem": "The rounded table is by what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 959,
        "problem": "Where is the couch end located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> by ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 960,
        "problem": "What is next to the couch end? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 961,
        "problem": "The small rounded table is next to what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 962,
        "problem": "The small circle table is next to what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 963,
        "problem": "The small round table is next to what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> ottoman </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 964,
        "problem": "What is next to the couch? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> 2 small round tables </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 965,
        "problem": "The small ottoman is next to what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> small round table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 966,
        "problem": "What is next to the tables? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> couches </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 967,
        "problem": "What type of couch is by the table at an angle? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> booth style couch </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 968,
        "problem": "Where is the medium couch located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind table </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0081_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 969,
        "problem": "What color soap dispenser is above the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 970,
        "problem": "Where is the white soap dispenser located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall right of sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 971,
        "problem": "What type of dispenser is on the left of a silver bar on the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> soap </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 972,
        "problem": "What is on the wall of the toilet seat cover dispenser? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trashcan </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 973,
        "problem": "What is under the counter top? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trashcan </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 974,
        "problem": "Where is the trash can located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> under bathroom counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 975,
        "problem": "What type of trash can is under the counter top? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> tall and grey </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 976,
        "problem": "What color soap dispenser is on the wall above the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 977,
        "problem": "What color sink is on the left of a soap dispenser? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 978,
        "problem": "Where is the white sink located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> left of white soap dispenser </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 979,
        "problem": "Where is the white shower seat located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> behind shower curtain </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 980,
        "problem": "What is on the wall above the counter top? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> soap dispenser </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 981,
        "problem": "Where is the black paper towel dispenser located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> above counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 982,
        "problem": "What type of toilet is to the right of a white trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 983,
        "problem": "Where is the white toilet located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to right of trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 984,
        "problem": "What is directly above the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> soap dispenser </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 985,
        "problem": "To the left of the sink counter is what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> paper towel dispenser </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 986,
        "problem": "To the left of the sink counter is a door with what kind of handle? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> silver handle </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 987,
        "problem": "What is next to the door? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> paper towel dispenser </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 988,
        "problem": "What is in the right corner of the room? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bathroom counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 989,
        "problem": "To the right of the toilet is what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trashcan </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 990,
        "problem": "What is attached to the wall on the left, just above the sink counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> paper towel dispenser </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 991,
        "problem": "Where is the paper towel dispenser located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> to left of sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 992,
        "problem": "What is under the sink? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 993,
        "problem": "Where is the black trash can located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> below sink </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 994,
        "problem": "Where is the white door located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> beside paper towel dispenser </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 995,
        "problem": "What color is the shower curtain? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 996,
        "problem": "Where is the white shower curtain? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of seat </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 997,
        "problem": "What type of trash can is on the floor under the bathroom counter? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> round </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 998,
        "problem": "Where is the white radiator mounted? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> on wall </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 999,
        "problem": "What type of window is on the wall in a bathroom stall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> glass </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1000,
        "problem": "Where is the glass window on the wall? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> in front of toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1001,
        "problem": "What is next to the window? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1002,
        "problem": "What is the trash can close to? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1003,
        "problem": "To what side of the door is the trash can located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> right </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1004,
        "problem": "What type of toilet is to the right of a trash can? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wall mounted </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1005,
        "problem": "What is to the right of the white toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1006,
        "problem": "What type of toilet is to the left of a roll of toilet paper? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> wall mounted </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1007,
        "problem": "What is to the left of the white toilet? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> trash can </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1008,
        "problem": "What type of radiator is to the right of a roll of toilet paper? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1009,
        "problem": "What is to the left of the white radiator? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> toilet </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1010,
        "problem": "What is the yellow sign? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> caution sign </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1011,
        "problem": "The white door is left of what? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> bathroom counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1012,
        "problem": "Where is the yellow sign located? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> against wall right of bathroom counter </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    },
    {
        "problem_id": 1013,
        "problem": "If you walk out of the shower stall and turn right, what will you see? ",
        "data_type": "scene",
        "problem_type": [
            "reasoning"
        ],
        "solution": "<answer> white door </answer>",
        "filename": "scene0084_00"
    }
]